So I'm trying to figure out where people think criticizing Zoran Mamdani is harmful to the
working class. Zoran Mamdani is a part of the Democratic Party. The Democratic Party couldn't
give a damn about the working class. This is shown in their policies. This is shown in the
fact that Kamala Harris ran an entire campaign that didn't say two words about the working class
and her policies. She focused on the middle class. So when we see folks saying Zoran Mamdani is not
radical, it's fascinating that you all don't understand that radical leftists are literally
all about the working class. It is about creating opportunities for the working class to no longer
have to be at the behest of the employer. It is about the working class being able to unionize.
It is about the working class getting access to that which they deserve because they are still
paying taxes. When it's said that you shouldn't question Mamdani or else he's not going to be
able to do what he needs to for the working class or my favorite, it's privilege that allows you to
question Mamdani. What that says to me is that you don't understand privilege. He is privileged
to have been elected mayor. He gets to be challenged. He gets to be questioned. And the working class
so often doesn't even have the time or the energy to demand for themselves because of the limitations
that have been placed upon them economically. So yes, he will be challenged to show up the way he said
he would. And all of you all who seem to think capitulating to MAGA, Zionists, and Democrats will
somehow beget favor for the working class. I really wonder what history you're looking at.
Because I don't see it. I don't see it. Cut it out. And this time I'm not yelling because of my
autism. I'm yelling because you're annoying. DC and Baltimore, you're up next. I'm outside y'all
doing what I can to decolonize minds on my mission-driven book tour for my new book, What Would
the Ancestors Say? They say books won't change the world. Tell that to every colonizer that burned them.
Come on out, be in community, buy a book, and get it signed. RSVP at amandaseals.com.